Guide to the General Frederick Steele Papers, 1845-1965 (inclusive), 1862-1868 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
- Series IA. Correspondence and papers of General Frederick Steele, 1845-1890.
  - Correspondence, 1865, February 20-28. (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - 22. 1865, Feb. 26.District of West Florida and South Alabama. S.O. No. 38, estract 3. Printed, s. F. W. Emery. E. H. Newton, temporary duty in field with FS.
    - 23. 1865, Feb. 26.Division of West Mississippi. Printed circular No. 5, s. John F. Lacey. Survey of horses, etc. for artillery.
    - 24. 1865, Feb. 26.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 23. Printed. Re: approvals for permits or safe conducts.
    - 25. 1865, Feb. 26.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 57, extract 3. Printed, s. Geo. L. Wilbur. FS to command Pensacola Bay troops.
    - 26. 1865, Feb. 26.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 28. Printed. Reorganization of 13th and 16th Army Corps under command of G. Granger and A. J. Smith.
    - 27. 1865, Feb. 27.District of West Florida and South Alabama. S.O. No. 39, extract 1. Printed, s. F. W. Emery. Leave of absence.
    - 28. 1865, Feb. 27.District of West Florida and South Alabama. S.O. No. 29, extract 4. Printed, s. F. W. Emery. Gordon to report to FS.
    - 29. 1865, Feb. 27.District of West Florida and South Alabama. S.O. No. 39, extract 5. Printed, s. F. W. Emery. Detached troops to rejoin respective companies.
    - 30. 1865, Feb. 27.3rd Brigade, Reserve Corps. G.O. No. 8. Printed, s. Geo. Monroe. Mustering.
    - 31. 1865, Feb. 28.District of West Florida, Barrancas, Fla. Consolidated Tri-Monthly Field Return of Troops under Asboth, s. Asboth.
    - 32. 1865, Feb. 28.District of West Florida, Barrancas, Fla. G.O. No. 23. Printed. Reprint of #20a.
    - 33. 1865, Feb. 28.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 24. Printed. Field allowance of ambulances, wagons and tents for hospital purposes.
    - 34. 1865, Feb. 28.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 25. Printed. Exchange of prisoners.
    - 35. 1965, Feb. 28.47th U.S. Colored Infantry. Roster of Commissioned Officers, s. J. Wm. Haight, Jr.
    - 36. 1865, Feb. 28.114th Regiment. Ohio Infantry Volunteers. Consolidated Report for Feb., s. John H. Kelly.
    - 37. 1865, Feb. 28.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 29. Printed. An act to increase the efficiency of the medical corps of the Army; to prevent military officers from interferring in elections and private resolution for D. Collett, Jr., deceased.
    - 38. 1865, Feb.John F. Lacey. ANS on docket re: consolidation of 28th and 37th Illinois Infantry.
  - Correspondence 1865, March 1-6. (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - 1. 1865, Mar. 1.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 26. Printed, s. John F. Lacey. Reorganization and relocation of troops.
    - 2. 1865, Mar. 1.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 27. Printed. General court martial of Luling.
    - 3. 1865, Mar. 1.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 28. Printed, s. John F. Lacey. Grierson to command Division Cavalry.
    - 4. 1865, Mar. 1.J. Wm. Haight, Jr. to John F. Lacey. ALS. Reports troops at Barrancas.
    - 5. 1865, Mar. 1.John H. Kelly to John F. Lacey. ALS. Transmitting reports.
    - 6. 1865, Mar. 1.13th Army Corps, Ft. Gaines, Ala. S.O. No. 3, extract 4. Printed, s. F. W. Emery. Surgeon Willis.
    - 7. 1865, Mar. 1.U.S. Forces, Barrancas, Fla. G.O. No. 1. Printed, s. John F. Lacey. Announces FS's staff officers.
    - 8. 1865, Mar. 2.District of West Florida and South Alabama. S.O. No. 42, extract 2. Printed, s. F. W. Emery. Recruits for colored regiments.
    - 9. 1865, Mar. 2.50th U.S. Colored Infantry. Roster of Commissioned Officers. Copy s. J. Wm. Haight
    - 10. 1865, Mar. 2.G[ordon] Granger to FS. LS. Wants C. C. Andrews ordered to occupy town of Pensacola to prevent smuggling.
    - 11. [1865, Mar. 2?].97th Illinois Volunteer Infantry. Roster of Commissioned Officers, s. J. William Haight, Jr.
    - 12. [1865, Mar. 2?].69th Battalion Indiana Infantry Volunteers. Roster of Commissioned Officers, s. J. William Haight, Jr.
    - 13. 1865, Mar. 2.H. K. Southwick to John C. Palfrey. ALS. Recommends not discharging 2nd Lt. Wm. P. Hazard. Docket: 3/11 ANS of C. T. Christensen, referral to FS.
    - 14. 1865, Mar. 2.13th Army Corps, Ft. Gaines, Ala. S.O. No. 4, extract 1. Printed, s. F. W. Emery. Orders for G. W. Richardson.
    - 15. [1865, Mar. 2?].25th Regiment U.S. Colored Infantry. Roster of Commissioned Officers, s. J. Wm. Haight, Jr.
    - 16. 1865, Mar. 3.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 29. Printed. Experts; tax on products of insurrectionary districts remitted.
    - 17. 1865, Mar. 3.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 30. Printed. Trade restrictions, information for Rebel deserters.
    - 18. 1865, Mar. 3.John P. Hawkins to Gen. Asboth. Copy. Equipping colored regiments (artillery).
    - 19. 1865, Mar. 3.War Department - A.G.O. S.O. No. 106, k extract 11. Stamped or s. E. D. Townsend. F. Sommer mustered out.
    - 20. 1865, Mar. 4.[Alexander] Asboth to F. W. Emery. Copy. Artillery needs and fortification.
    - 21. 1865, Mar. 4.[Alex.] Asboth to John P. Hawkins. Copy. Fortification and troop needs.
    - 22. 1865, Mar. 4.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 31. Printed, s. Geo. L. Wilbur. Officers' rations.
    - 23. 1865, Mar. 4.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 65, extract 16. Copy s. John F. Lacey. L. Rhoades.
    - 24. 1865, Mar. 4.1st Division, U.S. Colored Troops. Consolidated Tri-Monthly Field Return, s. John P. Hawkins
    - 25. 1865, Mar. 4.Timothy Owen to John F. Lacey. LS. Request for leave of absence.
    - 26. 1865, Mar. 4.Pensacola Dept., Ft. Pickens, Fla. Weekly Statement of Ordnance Stores, s. _. A. Metcalf.
    - 27. 1865, Mar. 4.2nd Division, 13th Army Corps. G.O. No. 1. Printed, s. George Monroe. Announces staff.
    - 28. 1865, Mar. 5.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 32. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Appointment of provost marshalls.
    - 29. 1865, Mar. 5.Charles S. McEntee to J. F. Lacey. ALS. Requests assignment of Gardner to 2nd Division, 13th Army Corps.
    - 30. 1865, Mar. 6.[Alex.] Asboth to John F. Lacey. NS. Transmits correspondence re: colored regiments.
    - 31. 1865, Mar. 6.Sam'l. T. Busey to F. W. Emery. LS. Transmits roster. Docket: n.d., NS of W. T. Spicely, 3/7 NS of C. C. Andrews.
    - 32. 1865, Mar. 6.Sam'l. T. Busey to John F. Lacey. LS. Same as #31. Docket: 3/[6] NS of W. T. Spicely, 3/6 NS of C. C. Andrews.
    - 33. 1865, Mar. 6.Dept. of the Gulf - Office Chief Signal Officer S.O. No. 16, extract 2. Copy s. E. P. Adams (X). W. F. Warren to report to FS.
    - 34. 1865, Mar. 6.1st Division, U.S. Colored Troops. G.O. No. 15. ADS of Sam'l B. Ferguson. No purchases during march by individuals.
    - 35. 1865, Mar. 6.F. M. Leflar to Jno. F. Lacey. LS. Requests send Lt. J. T. DeMar to procure arms and equipment. Docket: 3/6 NS of F. W. Moore, 3/6 NS of C. C. Andrews.
    - 36. 1865, Mar. 6.Charles S. McEntee to Jno. F. Lacey. LS. Requests teamsters.
  - Correspondence 1865, March 7-14. (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - 1. 1865, Mar. 7.Army and Division of West Mississippi. General Field Order [G.F.O.] No. 1. Printed. Keep on hand 3 days cooked rations, no land transportation spade and pick for temporary works.
    - 2. 1865, Mar. 7.[Alex.] Asboth to John F. Lacey. LS. Encloses scout reports [enclosures not present].
    - 3. 1865, Mar. 7.John Macy to [J. F.] Lacey. ALS. Report of ammunition.
    - 4. 1865, Mar. 7.2nd Division, 13th Army Corps. Morning Report. ADS of George Monroe, also s. C. C. Andrews.
    - 5-6. 1865, Mar. 7.76th U.S. Colored Infantry. Morning Report. ADS of W. R. High, also s. W. E. Nye. Separate docket: 2 ANS 3/8. Chas. W. Drew and J. P. Hawkins.
    - 7. 1865, Mar. 8.C. C. Andrews to John F. Lacey. LS. Sends mail carrier.
    - 8. 1865, Mar. 8.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 2. Printed. Regulations re: Amnesty Oath.
    - 9. 1865, Mar. 8.C. T. Christensen to FS. ANS. Canby to visit.
    - 10. 1865, Mar. 8.F. W. Moore to F. W. Emery. ANS. Transmittal. Docket: 3/8 NS of C. C. Andrews.
    - 11. [1865, Mar. 8].37th Illinois Infantry. Roster of Commissioned Officers. DS of R. Kennicott.
    - 12. 1865, Mar. 8.E. P. Nettleton to John F. Lacey. LS. Send roster [not enclosed].
    - 13. 1865, Mar. 8.13th Army Corps. G.O. No. 3. Printed, s. F. W. Emery. Equipment.
    - 14. 1865, Mar. 8.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 30. Printed. Claim agent's license.
    - 15. 1865, Mar. 8.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 31. Printed. Acts of Congress--enrolling and calling out national forces, prevent enlistment of persons charged with crimes, provide for a chief of staff to Lt. General, better organization of Subsistence Dept.
    - 16. 1865, Mar. 8.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 32. Printed. Rations for female nurses.
    - 17. 1865, Mar. 9.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 3. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Duties of provost marshalls in the field.
    - 18. 1865, Mar. 9.F. W. Emery to FS. ANS. Asks W. W. Todd to report to [Granger].
    - 19. 1865, Mar. 9.District of West Florida and South Alabama. S.O. No. 48, extract 1. Printed, s. F. W. Emery Post quarter masters and storage of baggage.
    - 20. 1865, Mar. 9.District of West Florida and South Alabama. S.O. No. 48, extract 3. Printed, s. F. W. Emery Appointment of a Medical Board.
    - 21. 1865, Mar. 9.1st Division, U.S. Colored Troops. Report of ambulances, s. John P. Hawkins.
    - 22. 1865, Mar. 9.13th Army Corps. S.O. No. 11, extract 4. Printed, s. F. W. Emery. Officers and men detailed for duty with Ambulance Corps, 1st Brigade, 2nd Division.
    - 23. 1865, Mar. 10.1st Division, U.S. Colored Troops. Tri-Monthly Report. ADS of Sam'l. B. Ferguson, also s. John P. Hawkins, ANS of John F. Lacey.
    - 24. 1865, Mar. 10.M. D. McAlister to P. C. Haines. Copy s. J. B. Dexter. Requests canvass-boat bridges.
    - 25. 1865, Mar. 10.[Pontonier] Corps. Tri-Monthly Report. ADS of Wm. Boyle.
    - 26. 1865, Mar. 10.G. W. Stepp. Certificate. Copy s. Timothy Owen. Owen unfit for duty.
    - 27. 1865, Mar. 10.2nd Division, 13th Army Corps. Tri-Monthly Report. ADS of George Monroe, also s. C. C. Andrews.
    - 28. 1865, Mar. 10.2nd Maine Cavalry. Morning Report. ADS of A. J. [Pickard], also s. E. W. Woodman.
    - 29. 1865, Mar. 10.U.S. Forces at Pensacola Bay. Tri-Monthly Report. DS of John F. Lacey. also s. FS.
    - 30. 1865, Mar. 11.C. C. Andrews to John F. Lacey. LS. Arrival at Pensacola, in ruins.
    - 31. 1865, Mar. 11.C. C. Andrews to J. F. Lacey. [Tel.], copy s. W. E. Warren. Arrival at Pensacola.
    - 32. 1865, Mar. 11[Alex.] Asboth to John F. Lacey. LS. Andrews' arrival at Pensacola.
    - 33. 1865, Mar. 11.[Alex.] Asboth to John F. Lacey. LS. Sent men to Pensacola to work on wharf.
    - 34. 1865, Mar. 11.C. T. Christensen to FS. ALS. Sends copies of G.O. No. 30 to be distributed within the rebel lines.
    - 35. 1865, Mar. 11.District of West Florida. S.O. No. 58, extract 4, s. J. Wm. Haight, Jr. Men working on new Barrancas wharf to help repair one at Pensacola.
    - 36. 1865, Mar. 11.[District of West Florida]. [Document?] 407. Copy. Mr. Gray to go to Pensacola.
    - 37. 1865, Mar. 11.Chas. W. Drew to John F. Lacey. NS. Transmittal.
    - 38. 1865, Mar. 11.John P. Hawkins to John F. Lacey. NS. Sends Tri-Monthly Return.
    - 39. 1865, Mar. 11.1st Division, U.S. Colored Troops. Tri-Monthly Field Return. ADS of John P. Hawkins. Enclosed in #38.
    - 40. 1865, Mar. 11.13th Army Corps. Printed circular No. 1. s. F. W. Emery. Ordnance reports.
    - 41. 1865, Mar. 11.U.S. Forces, Barrancas, Fla. Abstractsof reports of troops composing FS's command, s. John F. Lacey.
    - 42. 1865, Mar. 11.U.S. Forces, Barrancas, Fla. Abstract of reports of FS's command.
    - 43. 1865, Mar. 11.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 33. Printed. Congressional resolutions. Thanks to Gen. Thomas, encourage enlistments and promote efficiency of military forces.
    - 44. 1865, Mar. 11.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 34. Printed. Issue of flour to hospitals.
    - 45. 1865, Mar. 11.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 35. Printed. Presidential Proclamation--deserters to lose citizenship, etc.
    - 46. 1865, Mar. 12.[C. C.] Andrews to [J. F.] Lacey. Copy by W. F. Warren. Boat to bring cattle.
    - 47. 1865, Mar. 12.C. C. Andrews to John F. Lacey. ALS. Teams sent back to Barrancas.
    - 48. 1865, Mar. 13.[C. C.] Andrews to [J. F.] Lacey. Message, copy by E. P. Adams 9:30 a.m. Asks about supply steamer.
    - 49. 1865, Mar. 13.[C. C.] Andrews to [J. F.] Lacey. Message, copy by W. F. Warren 1:30 p.m. When will next boat leave for New Orleans.
    - 50. 1865, Mar. 13.[C. C.] Andrews to [J. F.] Lacey. Message, copy by W. F. Warren 5 p.m. No steamer, short rations.
    - 51. 1865, Mar. 13.C. C. Andrews to John F. Lacey. ALS. Sends article on fortifications of Mobile.
    - 52. 1865, Mar. 13.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 36. Printed. Special order re: Joint Committee to investigate Indian Affairs.
    - 53. 1865, Mar. 14.C. C. Andrews to John F. Lacey. LS. Mr. Gray--repair of wharf at Pensacola, railroad.
  - Correspondence 1865, March 15-19. (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - 1. 1865, Mar. 15.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 4. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. C. B. Comstock, special duty.
    - 2. 1865, Mar. 15.John F. Lacey to C. C. Andrews. ALS. Asks for private of 24th Indiana Infantry to report for duty as messenger orderly. Docket: 3/16 2 ANSs of George Monroe, 3/16 ANS of W. T. Spicely re: Pvt. Fielding A. Hyatt.
    - 3. 1865, Mar. 15.L. E. Norris to John F. Lacey. ANS. Withdraws request for detail of nurses.
    - 4. 1865, Mar. 15.13th Army Corps. G.F.O. No. 1. Printed, s. F. W. Emery. Engineer and assistant to march at head of most advanced detachment, keep journal of march.
    - 5. 1865, Mar. 15.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 37. Printed. Price of ration for POWs.
    - 6. 1865, Mar. 15.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 38. Printed. Modification of passport order.
    - 7. 1865, Mar. 15.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 39. Printed. Order concerning embalmers.
    - 8. 1865, Mar. 16.[C. C.] Andrews to [J. F.] Lacey. Message, copy by W. F. Warren. 10:55 a.m. Requests expert in track laying.
    - 9. 1865, Mar. 16.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 5. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Osterhaus, Chief of Staff to Canby.
    - 10. 1865, Mar. 16.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.E.O. No. 6. Printed. Requests military features of country from engineers.
    - 11. 1865, Mar. 16.C. T. Christensen to FS. ALS. Re: 25th, 82nd and 86th Regiments, U.S. Colored Infantry.
    - 12. 1865, Mar. 16.[S.] M. Eaton to E. R. S. Canby. ALS. Estimate of Confederate troops between Blakely and Pollard.
    - 13. 1865, Mar. 16.F. L. Hitchcock to John F. Lacey. NS. Sends roster [not enclosed].
    - 14. 1865, Mar. 16.A. M. Jackson to C. T. Christensen. Copy s. C. T. Christensen. Situation at Pollard, Confederate knowledge of Union movements.
    - 15. 1865, Mar. 16.2nd Illinois Cavalry. Morning Report. ADS of Frank Moore.
    - 16. 1865, Mar. 16.Geo, Tucker to John F. Lacey. NS. Transmittal.
    - 17. 1865, Mar. 17.[C. C.] Andrews to [J. F.] Lacey. Message, copy by W. F. Warren. 12 [noon?]. Tug for ammunition.
    - 18. 1865, Mar. 17.[C. C.] Andrews to [J. F.] Lacey. Message, copy by W. F. Warren. 3 p.m. Repairs on wharf.
    - 19. 1865, Mar. [17].[C. C.] Andrews to [J. F.] Lacey. Message, copy by E. P. Adams. 4:20 p.m. Sends tug back for ammunition.
    - 20. 1865, Mar. 17.[C. C.] Andrews to [J. F.] Lacey. Message, copy by E. P. Adams. 8 p.m. Asks about mail.
    - 21. 1865, Mar. 17.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 7. Printed. Districts of West Florida and South Alabama, Kilby Smith to relieve Granger.
    - 22. 1865, Mar. 17.[Alex.] Asboth to John F. Lacey. NS. Transmits troop information and Special Order.
    - 23. 1865, Mar. 17.District of West Florida. S.O. No. 64, extract 5, s. Asboth. Re: 82nd and 86th U.S. Colored Infantry, Cavalry Brigade and unbrigaded Regiments. Enclosed in #22.
    - 24. 1865, Mar. 17.R. H. Beaudry to John F. Lacey. ANS. Requests Teverbaugh be transferred to hospital in New Orleans.
    - 25. 1865, Mar. 17.District of West Florida and South Alabama. S.O. No. 52, extract 3. Printed, s. F. W. Emery. Assistant surgeon, J. T. Brown, to report to Asboth.
    - 26. 1865, Mar. 17.District of West Florida and South Alabama. S.O. No. 52, extract 4. Printed, s. F. W. Emery. Assistant L. E. Norris to 1st Florida Cavalry.
    - 27. 1865, Mar. 17.1st Division, U.S. Colored Infantry. S.O. No. 32, extract 2. ADS of Sam'l. B. Ferguson.
    - 27. 1865, Mar. 17.1st Division U.S. Colored Infantry. (cont.) S. A. Reed to turn over surplus ordnance. Docket: 3/18 ANS of Sam'l. A. Reed, NS of Asbot
    - 28. 1865, Mar. 17.J. B. McConaughy. Copy of contract with U.S. Army to act as medical officer of 48th U.S. Colored Infantry.
    - 29. 1865, Mar. 17.W. S. Pollard to George Monroe. NS. Request for pass for man to be mustered out. Docket: 3/17 NS of Francis A. Sears, NS of W. T. Spicely, 3/18 NS of C. C. Andrews.
    - 30. 1865, Mar. 17.13th Army Corps. S.O. No. 18, extract 4. Printed, s. F. W. Emery. Discharge.
    - 31. 1865, Mar. 17.13th Army Corps. S.O. No. 18. extract 5. Printed, s. F. W. Emery. Resignation and discharge.
    - 32. 1865, Mar. 17.G. E. [Yarrington] to John F. Lacey. NS. Transmittal.
    - 33. 1865, Mar. 18.[C. C] Andrews to [John F.] Lacey. Message, copy by E. P. Adams. 5:40 p.m. Platform car running.
    - 34. 1865, Mar. 18.C. C. Andrews to John F. Lacey. LS. Central wharf repaired, laid Railroad track.
    - 35. 1865, Mar. 18.Army and Division of West Mississippi. S.F.O. No. 11, extract 10. Copy re: ordnance report regulations when active operations have begun.
    - 36. 1865, Mar. 18.[Alex.] Asboth to John F. Lacey. LS. Number of troops left for guard and fatigue duty at Barrancas.
    - 37. 1865, Mar. 18.A. S. Badger to John F. Lacey. NS. Cover letter.
    - 38. 1865, Mar. 18.1st Regiment Louisiana Cavalry. Morning Report. ADS of Frank V. Kelly, also s. A. S. Badger. Enclosed in #37.
    - 39. 1865, Mar. 18.1st Division, U.S. Colored Troops. Circular No. 11. DS of Sam'l. B. Ferguson. Order of march of ambulances and trains.
    - 40. 1865, Mar. 18.E[ugene von] Kielmansegge to John F. Lacey. NS re: S.O. No. 12.
    - 41. 1865, Mar. 18.E. Kielmansegge to John F. Lacey. NS. Transmittal.
    - 42. 1865, Mar. 18.E. Kielmansegge to John F. Lacey. NS. Transmittal.
    - 43. 1865, Mar. 18.1st Regiment Florida Cavalry. Morning Field Return. ADS of Fred Jost, also s. E. Kielmansegge. Enclosed in #42.
    - 44. 1865, Mar. 18.1st Regiment Florida Cavalry. Morning Report. ADS of Fred Jost, also s. E. Kielmansegge. Enclosed in #42.
    - 45. 1865, Mar. 18.E. P. Nettleton to John F. Lacey. NS. Transmittal.
    - 46. 1865, Mar. 18.31st Massachusetts Mounted Infantry. Morning Report. DS of James M. Stewart and E. P. Nettleton. Enclosed in #45.
    - 47. 1865, Mar. 18.W. E. Nye to John F. Lacey. NS. Transmittal. Docket: 3/18 ANS of Chas W. Drew.
    - 48. 1865, Mar. 18.2nd New York Veteran Cavalry. Morning Report. DS of W. D. Doty and Edward Van Voast.
    - 49. 1865, Mar. 18.Separate Cavalry Brigade. Tri-Monthly Field Return. ADS of Rob't. Barber, also s. M. N. Chrysler.
    - 50. 1865, Mar. 18.FS to L. Thomas. NS. Sends G.O. No. 2. Docket: 3/31 NS of E. D. Townsend.
    - 51. 1865, Mar. 18.E. W. Woodman to John F. Lacey. NS. Transmittal.
    - 52-53. 1865, Mar. 19.Adams Express Co. to FS. 2 receipts for gold and notes.
    - 54. 1865, Mar. 19.[C. C.] Andrews to [J. F.] Lacey. Message, copy by E. P. Adams. 10:15 a.m. Re: embarking 2nd Maine.
    - 55. 1865, Mar. 19.Army and Division of West Mississippi. S.F.O. No. 12, extract 4. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Make-up of Division of Colored Infantry.
    - 56. 1865, Mar. 19.Army and Division of West Mississippi. S.F.O. No. 12, extract 7. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Maj. Perry to report to W. F. Smith.
    - 57. 1865, Mar. 19.Edward Van Voast to John F. Lacey. NS. Corrects roster.
  - Correspondence 1865, March 20-24. (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - 1. 1865, Mar. 20.C. C. Andrews to John F. Lacey. LS. Arrival of 3rd Brigade, 2nd Division, 13th Army Corps; road conditions, etc.
    - 2. 1865, Mar. 20.1st Division, U.S. Colored Troops. Tri-Monthly Report. DS of Sam'l. B. Ferguson and John P. Hawkins.
    - 3. 1865, Mar. 20.E. V. Hitch to John F. Lacey. ANS. Transmittal.
    - 4. 1865, Mar. 20.Separate Cavalry Brigade. Tri-Monthly Field Return. ADS of E. V. Hitch. Enclosed in #3.
    - 5. 1865, Mar. 20.2nd Division, 13th Army Corps. Tri-Monthly Report. ADS of George Monroe, also s. C. C. Andrews.
    - 6. 1865, Mar. 20.A. B. Spurling to John F. Lacey. ALS. Plans for Special Cavalry expedition.
    - 7. 1865, Mar. 20.U.S. Forces operating from Pensacola Bay. Tri-Monthly Field Return.
    - 8. 1865, Mar. 20.U.S. Forces operating from Pensacola Bay. Tri-Monthly Morning Report. DS of John F. Lacey and FS.
    - 9. 1865, Mar. 20.U.S. Forces operating from Pensacola Bay. Troop Strength. DS of John F. Lacey.
    - 10. 1865, Mar. 20.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 40. Printed. Exchange POWs.
    - 11. 1865, Mar. 20.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 41. Printed. 19th Army Corps discontinued.
    - 12. 1865, Mar. 20.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 42. Printed. Gibbon to command 24th Army Corps.
    - 13. 1865, Mar. 21.G. B. Beach to E. V. Hitch. ALS. Loss of 3 men. Docket: 3/22 NS of T. J. Lucas.
    - 14. 1865, Mar. 21.1st Division, U.S. Colored Infantry. Tri-Monthly Field Return. DS of John P. Hawkins.
    - 15. 1865, Mar. 21.Separate Cavalry Brigade. Tri-Monthly Report. DS of T. J. Lucas and E. V. Hitch.
    - 16. 1865, Mar. 21.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 43. Printed. Organization and assignment of 1st and 2nd Battalions of Veteran Reserve Corps.
    - 17. 1865, Mar. 21.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 44. Printed. Dept. of Arkansas and Indian Territory transferred to Division of Missouri.
    - 18. 1865, Mar. 21.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 45. Printed. Acts of Congress--appropriations for support of army thru June '66, incorporation of national military asylum for totally disabled of the volunteer forces.
    - 19. 1865, Mar. 21.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 46. Printed. Release of civilians from parole.
    - 20. 1865, Mar. 21.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 47. Printed. Exchanged officers and men to report at parole depots.
    - 21. 1865, Mar. 22.D_____ to Gen. Asboth. Copy (official signature illegible). Report of rebels at Blakely and Federal troops at Spanish Fort.
    - 22. 1865, Mar. 22.T. J. Lucas to J. F. Lacey. LS. Progress of march, road conditions and rivers.
    - 23. 1865, Mar. 23.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 8, s. Alfred Fredberg. Rules for collection of supplies in the field.
    - 24. 1865, Mar. 23.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 8. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Copy of #23.
    - 25. 1865, Mar. 23.Army and Division of West Mississippi. S.F.O. No. 16, extract 4, s. Alfred Fredberg. Packages for commanding officers.
    - 26. 1865, Mar. 23.[Alex.] Asboth to John F. Lacey. LS. Acknowledgement and transmittal of information.
    - 27. 1865, Mar. 6 and 7.A. B. Spurling to A. Asboth. Copy. Rebels at Canoe Station, Blakely, Greenwoods, Mobile, Milton, Fla. and Pollard. Enclosed in #26.
    - 28. 1865, Mar. 23.John P. Hawkins to J. F. Lacey. ALS. Repair work on bridge.
    - 29. 1865, Mar. 23.John F. Lacey to T. J. Lucas. ANS. Inquires about 3 missing men. ANS of E. V. Hitch on verso.
    - 30. 1865, Mar. 23.E. H. Newton to FS. ANS. Wants axes for Hawkins' Pioneer Company.
    - 31. 1865, Mar. 24.C. C. Andrews to John F. Lacey. NS. Re: Cooper's Landing.
    - 32. 1865, Mar. 24.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 9, s. Alfred Fredberg. Limits animals' grain ration.